Secretary of the Faculty for Arts, Sciences and Engineering Records UA037
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Faculty meeting minutes, 1854 -- 2019; UA037.001; 9.4 Linear Feet; 55 Volumes; 431 Digital Object(s); 938 Megabytes 429 of 431 digital objects comprise 938 megabytes.
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2014 -- 2015; UA037.001111; 35 Megabytes; 48 Digital Object(s)
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2014 October 15; UA037.001115; 86.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2014 October 22; UA037.001116; 7 Megabytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula Committee agenda, 2014 October 22; UA037.001117; 54 Kilobytes
    - Primary major proposal with appendices, 2014 October 22; UA037.001118; 5.8 Megabytes
    - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering faculty work-life resources, 2014 November 05; UA037.001119; 66.7 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs meeting agenda, 2014 November 05; UA037.001120; 93.9 Kilobytes
    - Revised part-time faculty union contract presentation, 2014 November 05; UA037.001121; 49.2 Kilobytes
    - Work-life summary card for liaisons, Fall 2014, 2014 November 05; UA037.001122; 33.9 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College curricula committee agenda, 2014 November 19; UA037.001123; 27.9 Kilobytes
    - New and recent changes at Tisch Library, 2014 November 19; UA037.001124; 155.2 Kilobytes
    - Tisch Library strategic plan, draft version 5, 2014 November 19; UA037.001125; 127.1 Kilobytes
    - Office of Equal Opportunity announcement information, 2014 December 10; UA037.001126; 142.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences research affairs reorganization, chairs' and directors' meeting presentation, 2014 December 10; UA037.001127; 369.5 Kilobytes
    - Professor of the Practice proposed changes to faculty by-laws and handbook, 2014 December 10; UA037.001128; 30 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs agenda, revised, 2014 December 10; UA037.001129; 33.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 February 04; UA037.001130; 149.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 February 18; UA037.001131; 325.3 Kilobytes
    - Credit hour compliance presentation, 2015 February 18; UA037.001132; 77.8 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee proposal for make-up snow days, 2015 February 18; UA037.001133; 193.5 Kilobytes
    - Professor of the practice proposed changes, 2015 February 18; UA037.001134; 210.9 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs agenda, 2015 March 04; UA037.001135; 33.6 Kilobytes
    - Department chair meeting notes, 2015 March 04; UA037.001136; 19.2 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 March 11; UA037.001137; 557.8 Kilobytes
    - Faculty governance memo to all full-time faculty, 2015 March 11; UA037.001138; 93.4 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula Committee agenda, 2015 March 11; UA037.001139; 248.2 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula Committee agenda addendum, 2015 March 11; UA037.001140; 15.4 Kilobytes
    - Resolution on the task force election, 2015 March 11; UA037.001141; 13.5 Kilobytes
    - Tufts learning objectives for distribution requirements, 2015 March 11; UA037.001142; 62.9 Kilobytes
    - Commencement assignment spreadsheet, 2015 March 01; UA037.001143; 31.5 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs agenda, 2015 April 01; UA037.001144; 47.7 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences handout, 2015 April 01; UA037.001145; 104.2 Kilobytes
    - Guidelines for chairs on meeting to discuss evaluations, 2015 April 01; UA037.001146; 62.5 Kilobytes
    - Provost Council presentation, 2015 April 01; UA037.001147; 1.9 Megabytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 April 08; UA037.001148; 83.3 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting presentation, 2015 April 08; UA037.001149; 14.6 Megabytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 April 15; UA037.001150; 75.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 April 15; UA037.001151; 733.5 Kilobytes
    - A quick guide to depositing faculty work in the Tufts Digital Library, 2015 April 15; UA037.001152; 242.5 Kilobytes
    - Learning Outcomes Assessment Committee proposal handout, 2015 April 15; UA037.001153; 172.7 Kilobytes
    - Learning Outcomes Assessment Committee proposal handout, 2015 April 15; UA037.001154; 171.4 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College curricula agenda, 2015 April 15; UA037.001155; 63.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 May 06; UA037.001156; 586.4 Kilobytes
    - Curriculum Committee agenda, 2015 May 06; UA037.001157; 69 Kilobytes
    - Working proposals: indirect cost recovery and return presentation, 2015 May 06; UA037.001158; 1.2 Megabytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 May 14; UA037.001159; 117.4 Kilobytes
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2015 -- 2016; UA037.001160; 34.6 Megabytes; 39 Digital Object(s)
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 September 16; UA037.001161; 266.5 Kilobytes
    - Report on the State of School presentation, 2015 September 16; UA037.001162; 54 Kilobytes
    - Department chair meeting minutes, 2015 October 07; UA037.001163; 1.3 Megabytes
    - Disability and religious accommodations: what faculty, managers, and supervisors need to know, 2015 October 07; UA037.001164; 1.2 Megabytes
    - Introduction to digital measures for chairs, 2015 October 07; UA037.001165; 64 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 October 21; UA037.001166; 425 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricular Committee October 2015 proposals, 2015 October 21; UA037.001167; 47.3 Kilobytes
    - Board of Advisors October 2015 working draft presentation, 2015 November 04; UA037.001168; 20.2 Megabytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 November 04; UA037.001169; 275.5 Kilobytes
    - Tufts Plus: the updated version of 4 + 1 degrees presentation, 2015 November 04; UA037.001170; 74 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs minutes, 2015 November 10; UA037.001171; 41.7 Kilobytes
    - SMFA@Tufts: academic vision presentation, 2015 November 18; UA037.001172; 232.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 November 18; UA037.001173; 833.6 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula agenda, 2015 November 18; UA037.001174; 32.9 Kilobytes
    - SMFA@Tufts presentation, 2015 November 18; UA037.001175; 3.5 Megabytes
    - Science, Technology, and Society program proposal, 2015 November 18; UA037.001176; 114.2 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 November 19; UA037.001177; 392.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2015 December 09; UA037.001178; 211.1 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs minutes, 2015 December 16; UA037.001179; 40.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, redacted, 2016 January 27; UA037.001180; 251.2 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs minutes, 2016 February 10; UA037.001181; 45.6 Kilobytes
    - Intellectual property ownership of course materials presentation, 2016 February 10; UA037.001182; 696.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2016 February 17; UA037.001183; 244.7 Kilobytes
    - Revenue generating ideas presentation, 2016 February 17; UA037.001184; 2.2 Megabytes
    - Department chairs minutes, 2016 March 02; UA037.001185; 46.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2016 March 16; UA037.001186; 245.8 Kilobytes
    - Revised interim report of the faculty governance working group, 2016 March 16; UA037.001187; 43 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula agenda, 2016 March 16; UA037.001188; 80.4 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences graduate student career services presentation, 2016 April 06; UA037.001189; 102.9 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2016 April 06; UA037.001190; 134.3 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs minutes, 2016 April 13; UA037.001191; 43.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2016 April 20; UA037.001192; 226.9 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula agenda, final revision, 2015 April 20; UA037.001193; 45.5 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2016 May 11; UA037.001194; 268.6 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee proposal, 2016 May 11; UA037.001195; 46.7 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula agenda, 2016 May 11; UA037.001196; 119.3 Kilobytes
    - Faculty workload recommendations for discussion, 2016 May 11; UA037.001197; 265.9 Kilobytes
    - Workload presentation, Arts and Sciences faculty meeting, 2016 May 11; UA037.001198; 68.4 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, redacted, 2016 May 19; UA037.001199; 168 Kilobytes
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2016 -- 2017; UA037.001200; 17.5 Megabytes; 45 Digital Object(s)
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2016 September 14; UA037.001201; 41.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2016 September 28; UA037.001202; 107 Kilobytes
    - Senate by-laws draft, 2016 September 28; UA037.001203; 51.3 Kilobytes
    - Faculty workload proposal, 2016 September 28; UA037.001204; 57.9 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2016 October 05; UA037.001205; 131.8 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences strategic goals, 2016 October 05; UA037.001206; 2.6 Megabytes
    - Masters Program in Diversity and Inclusion Leadership working draft, 2016 October 05; UA037.001207; 103.4 Kilobytes
    - Fletcher School and School of Arts and Sciences economic policy joint doctoral program proposal, 2016 October 05; UA037.001208; 57.4 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2016 October 26; UA037.001209; 3.3 Megabytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula agenda for Arts and Sciences meeting, 2016 October 26; UA037.001210; 44.1 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences year in philanthropy PowerPoint, 2016 October 26; UA037.001211; 1.4 Megabytes
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2016 November 02; UA037.001212; 43 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2016 November 30; UA037.001213; 321.6 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2016 December 07; UA037.001214; 39.9 Kilobytes
    - Research administration system presentation, 2016 December 07; UA037.001215; 808 Kilobytes
    - Research professor guidelines, 2016 December 07; UA037.001216; 30.6 Kilobytes
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges form E1A inventory of educational effectiveness indicators, academic year 2011/2012 Arts and Sciences report, 2017 January 25; UA037.001217; 241.8 Kilobytes
    - Course list development and summer instructor compensation, version 4, 2017 January 25; UA037.001218; 27.1 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2017 January 25; UA037.001219; 63.6 Kilobytes
    - Making assessment more explicit, E series forms, 2017 January 25; UA037.001220; 27.7 Kilobytes
    - Student tuition and fees, version 1, 2017 January 25; UA037.001221; 100.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2017 February 01; UA037.001222; 138.4 Kilobytes
    - Draft description and workload for Arts and Sciences senate representation, 2017 February 01; UA037.001223; 18.6 Kilobytes
    - Report on budget situation, 2017 February 01; UA037.001224; 58 Kilobytes
    - The Conversation, US presentation, 2017 February 01; UA037.001225; 5.1 Megabytes
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2017 February 15; UA037.001226; 34 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2017 February 22; UA037.001227; 210.4 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula agenda, 2017 February 22; UA037.001228; 43 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agenda, 2017 March 08; UA037.001229; 257.2 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs minutes, 2017 March 15; UA037.001230; 30.3 Kilobytes
    - Advising options handout, 2017 April 05; UA037.001231; 19.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2017 April 05; UA037.001232; 211.9 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula agenda, 2017 April 05; UA037.001233; 303.8 Kilobytes
    - Proposed changes to Arts and Sciences Senate representation, 2017 April 05; UA037.001234; 21 Kilobytes
    - Proposed changes to summa honors, 2017 April 05; UA037.001235; 112.3 Kilobytes
    - Blue course evaluations at Tufts, 2017 April 19; UA037.001236; 545.1 Kilobytes
    - Blue course evaluations at Tufts, 2017 April 19; UA037.001237; 454.7 Kilobytes
    - Blue course evaluations - DEMO, Amity N. Law (Su17-FAH-0053-A-Origins Of Modern Art), 2017 April 19; UA037.001238; 317.1 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2017 April 19; UA037.001239; 33.5 Kilobytes
    - University-wide teaching conference schedule, 2017 April 19; UA037.001240; 130 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2017 May 10; UA037.001241; 282.3 Kilobytes
    - Curricula agenda, 2017 May 10; UA037.001242; 47.8 Kilobytes
    - Digital arts and humanities roundtable presentation, 2017 May 10; UA037.001243; 226.9 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee proposal for clarifying rules for senior honors theses, 2017 May 10; UA037.001244; 25.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2017 May 18; UA037.001245; 180.7 Kilobytes
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2017 -- 2018; UA037.001246; 659 Megabytes; 53 Digital Object(s)
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2017 September 20; UA037.001247; 238.2 Kilobytes
    - General education assessment for equity and inclusion, 2017 September 20; UA037.001248; 478.2 Kilobytes
    - Research update, 2017 September 20; UA037.001249; 60.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2017 September 27; UA037.001250; 339.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences financial update, 2017 September 27; UA037.001251; 70.2 Kilobytes
    - Curricula agenda, 2017 September 27; UA037.001252; 319.1 Kilobytes
    - Research update, 2017 September 27; UA037.001253; 82.6 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agenda, 2017 October 11; UA037.001254; 259.7 Kilobytes
    - Department chair minutes, 2017 October 25; UA037.001255; 264.1 Kilobytes
    - Changes to the part-time collective bargaining agreement, summary sheet for chairs and department advisors, 2017 October 25; UA037.001256; 176.1 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2017 November 01; UA037.001257; 413 Kilobytes
    - Compliance overview, 2017 November 01; UA037.001258; 710.4 Kilobytes
    - Campus crisis response training presentation, 2017 November 01; UA037.001259; 523 Megabytes
    - Clinical and Translational Science Institute (CTSI) handouts and 2015 annual report, 2017 November 01; UA037.001260; 3 Megabytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College curriculua agenda, 2017 November 01; UA037.001261; 32.8 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs minutes, 2017 November 29; UA037.001262; 361.6 Kilobytes
    - Office of Equal Opportunity handout, 2017 November 29; UA037.001263; 1 Megabytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2017 December 06; UA037.001264; 442.2 Kilobytes
    - Counseling and mental health service update, 2017 December 06; UA037.001265; 989.2 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College curriculum committee agenda, 2017 December 06; UA037.001266; 26.7 Kilobytes
    - Tisch Library reference, consultations, and instruction report, 2017 December 06; UA037.001267; 115.4 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2018 January 31; UA037.001268; 351 Kilobytes
    - Faculty awards graphs, 2018 January 31; UA037.001269; 151 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula agenda, 2018 January 31; UA037.001270; 38.7 Kilobytes
    - Strategic plan update, 2018 January 31; UA037.001271; 1.2 Megabytes
    - Department chairs, 2018 February 14; UA037.001272; 541.6 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs minutes, 2018 February 14; UA037.001273; 174.7 Kilobytes
    - Faculty diversity handouts, 2018 February 14; UA037.001274; 23.6 Kilobytes
    - Mental Health Task Force background materials, 2018 February 14; UA037.001275; 496.7 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting, 2018 February 21; UA037.001276; 830.7 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2018 February 21; UA037.001277; 144.7 Kilobytes
    - Request for Action by the Policy and Program Committee for post-baccalaureate program in mathematics, 2018 February 21; UA037.001278; 208.2 Kilobytes
    - Request for Action by the Policy and Program Committee for GIS certificate, 2018 February 21; UA037.001279; 263.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2018 March 07; UA037.001280; 189.1 Kilobytes
    - Committee on student life policy review presentation to Arts and Sciences faculty, 2018 March 07; UA037.001281; 52.6 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula agenda, 2018 March 07; UA037.001282; 78.7 Kilobytes
    - Preferred name policy, July 2017, 2018 March 14; UA037.001283; 24 Kilobytes
    - Canvas for Arts and Sciences department chairs, 2018 March 14; UA037.001284; 16.3 Megabytes
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2018 March 14; UA037.001285; 154.4 Kilobytes
    - Faculty diversity handouts, 2018 March 14; UA037.001286; 742.4 Kilobytes
    - Full-time faculty size by department, 2018 March 14; UA037.001287; 360.1 Kilobytes
    - Gender unicorn graphic by Trans Student Educational Resources (TSER), 2018 March 14; UA037.001288; 390.7 Kilobytes
    - Non-discrimination policy, 2018 March 14; UA037.001289; 290.9 Kilobytes
    - Pronoun primer, 2018 March 14; UA037.001290; 118.7 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs minutes, 2018 April 18; UA037.001291; 193.7 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs faculty meeting slides on graduate student union bargaining, 2018 April 18; UA037.001292; 51.8 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agenda, 2018 April 18; UA037.001293; 259.6 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences vote, 2018 April 18; UA037.001294; 109.9 Kilobytes
    - Mental Health Task Force overview presentation, 2018 April 18; UA037.001295; 2.2 Megabytes
    - Career Center PowerPoint, 2018 May 09; UA037.001296; 102 Megabytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2018 May 09; UA037.001297; 231.5 Kilobytes
    - Simin Strategic plan update, 2018 May 09; UA037.001298; 4.7 Megabytes
    - Arts and Sciences honors meeting minutes, 2018 May 17; UA037.001299; 94.6 Kilobytes
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2018 -- 2019; UA037.001300; 37.6 Megabytes; 49 Digital Object(s)
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agenda, 2018 September 26; UA037.001301; 261.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2018 September 26; UA037.001302; 141 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College agenda, 2018 September 26; UA037.001303; 442.2 Kilobytes
    - Pronoun primer, 2018 September 26; UA037.001304; 118.7 Kilobytes
    - Psychology proposals, 2018 September 26; UA037.001305; 18.6 Kilobytes
    - Budget management presentation, 2018 October 10; UA037.001306; 388 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs minutes, 2018 October 10; UA037.001307; 164.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agenda, 2018 October 24; UA037.001308; 259.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2018 October 24; UA037.001309; 183.7 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences financial update, 2018 October 24; UA037.001310; 816.4 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curriculum Committee agenda, 2018 October 24; UA037.001311; 495.1 Kilobytes
    - Research and scholarship strategic plan, 2018 October 24; UA037.001312; 4.6 Megabytes
    - Faculty-student mentoring at the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences presentation, 2018 October 31; UA037.001313; 1.1 Megabytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting, 2018 October 31; UA037.001314; 2.4 Megabytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2018 October 31; UA037.001315; 211.2 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2018 November 14; UA037.001316; 243.5 Kilobytes
    - General academic advising: Educational Policy Committee's current thinking, 2018 November 14; UA037.001317; 59.2 Kilobytes
    - Consistency of faculty titles across Arts and Sciences presentation, 2018 November 14; UA037.001318; 94.3 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2018 November 28; UA037.001319; 147.7 Kilobytes
    - Secondary majors and SMFA dual-degree students, proposal from educational policy committee, 2018 November 28; UA037.001320; 40.5 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curriculum Committee agenda, revised, 2018 November 28; UA037.001321; 640.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences fiscal year 2019 budget measures, 2018 December 05; UA037.001322; 222.1 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2018 December 05; UA037.001323; 148.5 Kilobytes
    - Strategic plan, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting PowerPoint, 2019 January 30; UA037.001324; 2.5 Megabytes
    - January Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agenda, 2019 January 30; UA037.001325; 99.8 Kilobytes
    - Gen Z and the future of work presentation, 2019 February 13; UA037.001326; 12.2 Megabytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2019 February 13; UA037.001327; 128.2 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curriculum Committee agenda, 2019 February 13; UA037.001328; 365.3 Kilobytes
    - Senate update, 2019 February 13; UA037.001329; 43.7 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2019 February 20; UA037.001330; 79.2 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences mentoring, 2019 February 20; UA037.001331; 1.7 Megabytes
    - Incorporating information literary assessment into assigments handout, 2019 February 20; UA037.001332; 82 Kilobytes
    - Incorporating assessment into classes and assignments presentation, 2019 February 20; UA037.001333; 931.9 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College curricula agenda, 2019 March 05; UA037.001334; 249.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2019 March 06; UA037.001335; 211.7 Kilobytes
    - Draft by-laws of the faculty of the School of Arts and Sciences, 2019 March 06; UA037.001336; 202.9 Kilobytes
    - Educational Policy Committee proposal for SMFA combined-degree residence requirement, 2019 March 06; UA037.001337; 41.4 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs meeting minutes, 2019 March 13; UA037.001338; 132.2 Kilobytes
    - Instituional review board process presentation, 2019 March 13; UA037.001339; 546.6 Kilobytes
    - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agenda, 2019 April 10; UA037.001340; 259.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty senate update, 2019 April 17; UA037.001341; 167.8 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2019 April 17; UA037.001342; 102 Kilobytes
    - Liberal Arts and Jackson College Curricula agenda part II, voting agenda, 2019 April 17; UA037.001343; 290.6 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences department chairs and program directors meeting minutes, 2019 May 08; UA037.001344; 133.9 Kilobytes
    - Learning Outcomes Assessment Committee presentation, 2019 May 08; UA037.001345; 124.1 Kilobytes
    - Performance development review Arts and Sciences chairs, 2019 May 08; UA037.001346; 1.3 Megabytes
    - Post award office update presentation, 2019 May 08; UA037.001347; 3.8 Megabytes